

# **Blair Seivers**

Raleigh, NC 27612 (919) 671-1705 blair.seivers@gmail.com

# WEBSITE, PORTFOLIO. **PROFILES**

instagram.com/adventure.brindles

# PROFESSIONAL () **SUMMARY**

Compassionate and detail oriented virtual assistant with demonstrated success in organizing services based on individual business requirements. Highly experienced in maintaining books for multiple businesses. Strong organizational skills with a creative flair. Experience and knowledge of multiple computer programs and project management software. Additionally have tons of experience with exercising and training different types of animals and collaborating with owners to deliver top-notch care.

#### SKILLS

- Strong organizational skills
- Very creative
- Works well in fast paced environment
- Time Management

- Interpersonal communication
- Resourceful
- Computer skills

#### WORK HISTORY

#### **DOG SITTER**

06/2016 to CURRENT

## Self Employed | Raleigh, NC

- Boarding, Daycare and Dog walking services
- Training and reinforcing good behavior
- Booking appointments
- Established online presence
- Maintain social media pages
- Increased business through online advertisements
- Designed promotional stickers
- Calendar management
- Ordering supplies & tracking inventory
- Keeping financial records

## HAIR STYLIST

12/2006 to CURRENT

## Self Employed | Raleigh, NC

- Customer service
- Established self employed business just 1 1/2 years out of school.
- Maintaining social media pages
- Scheduling appointments

- Managing 2 or 3 clients at once.
- Calendar management
- Organizing client data records
- Tracking inventory
- Buying and ordering supplies
- Keeping financial records

#### **OFFICE ASSISTANT**

01/2010 to 03/2020

### Toni Rocker, CPA | Raleigh, NC

- Organize files
- Prepare and send out mailers to over 300 clients
- Process tax returns
- File extension requests
- Customer service
- Calendar management

WAITRESS 07/2008 to 07/2013

# BrickHouse | Raleigh, NC

- Customer service
- Keeping multiple tables and orders organized
- Working quickly and efficiently in fast paced environment
- Working well as a team with co workers
- Tracking sales

**EDUCATION** 

**Certification** | Virtual Assistant

90 Day VA, Online

Cosmetology License | Cosmetology

11/2006

Mitchell's Hair Styling Academy, Raleigh, NC